T. James Crawford papers, 1940-1987 C468
Indiana University Archives
T. James Crawford papers
1940-1987
Indiana University Archives
Crawford, T. James (Thomas James)
C468
6.6 cubic feet 8 boxes
T. James Crawford was a Professor Emeritus of Business and Education at Indiana University. He published many text books but is best known for his co-authored work on typing, 20th Century Typewriting. The collection consists primarily of his teaching materials as well as correspondence, records related to professional activities, and publishing.
Access Restrictions
Two folders have been restricted: the Dr. H. D. David, 1970-1986 (office files) and the Personal Correspondence, 1958-1963 (Series: Teaching, Subseries: General)
Advance notice is required for access to the collection.
Biographical Note
T. James Crawford was born on December 14, 1916 in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania and died on August 15, 2000 in Bloomington, Indiana. Crawford grew up in the Pittsburgh area where he would later receive both his bachelor's and master's degrees at the University of Pittsburgh. It was while he was attending the University of Pittsburg that he met D.D. Leesenberry, with whom he would later coauthor 20th Century Typewriting. Crawford would later return to the University of Pittsburgh to obtain his doctoral degree.
In May of 1942, after serving as a faculty member at the University of Pittsburgh and the Women's College of the University of North Carolina, Crawford came to Indiana University. His intention was to join the IU Summer Session faculty but instead was given the duty of assisting with the organization of the U.S. Naval Training School which was being started as a result of the war effort. While not yet in active duty, he became supervisor of instruction in the U.S. Navy School for Yeomen and Storekeepers. In that position, he helped design a program for the first group of WAVES that had been recruited by the Navy. In December of 1942 Crawford was provided his orders for active duty as a supply officer for a Seabee battalion. He would serve overseas for nearly two years.
Following the war, Crawford returned to IU as a faculty lecturer in the School of Business. During his tenure at IU, he was chairman of the department of administrative systems and business education for 15 years. Additionally, he worked to initiate educational television by assisting in the development of some of the first television courses via the IU television network. Crawford's professional associations were with the Indiana Business Educators Club, the National Association for Business Teacher Education, and the State Association for Business Education for which he served for a period of time as president. Crawford retired from Indiana University in 1987.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in four series: Teaching, Correspondence, Professional activities, and Publishing.
Scope and Content Note
The T. James Crawford papers are organized into four series - Teaching, Correspondence, Professional activities and Publishing.
The Teaching series is further organized into four subseries - Course files, Shorthand, Typing and General. The first subseries, Course files, is listed by the class number, alphabetically and numerically (e.g., B 503, B 504, etc.). Folders with the same class number are then listed chronologically. The contents of the Course files subseries include copies of examinations and reading lists, which directly relate to his classes in business education, shorthand and typing. The Shorthand subseries is arranged in alphabetical order and contains methods related to shorthand, exams, and shorthand drills. Similarly, the Typing subseries is arranged alphabetically. It contains articles related to typing performance, drills, and exams. The General subseries is arranged alphabetically by folder title and is comprised of teaching schedules for faculty and enrollment information, as well as teaching materials that are not specific to any particular class such as bibliographies and class handouts.
Because the Teaching series contains student information, it is restricted. Folders requested by researchers will first be reviewed by an archivist as they may contain personal information regarding students.
The Correspondence series is arranged alphabetically by folder heading. The bulk of the correspondence consists of departmental communications as well as correspondence with the various professional organizations in which Crawford was involved.
The Professional activities series is further organized into two subseries, Professional organizations and conferences and General, both arranged alphabetically by folder heading. The Professional organizations and conferences subseries documents Crawford's activities in the Administrative Management Society, Indiana Business Education Association, and the National Association for Business Teacher Education. Additionally, this subseries contains records relating to conferences that Crawford attended such as those of the North Carolina Business Education Association and the Administrative Management Society. This subseries is made up mostly of short publications prepared by those organizations, directories, guidelines, and meeting notes. The General subseries consists primarily of folders containing records relating to Crawford's faculty activities, such as records pertaining to committee work, faculty annual reports, and course proposals.
The Publishing series is arranged alphabetically. The series is comprised records related to the publication of 20th Century Typewriting, and includes an 8 volume set of a braille edition.
Related Material
Related photographs may be available in the University Archives Photographs Database
Acquisition Information
Accession numbers: 2001/042
Provenance
Papers were boxed up at the School of Business in 2001.
Appraisal
During processing, it was determined that in the course files sub-series syllabi and course outlines would be retained however exams files were removed as they mostly contained restricted student information. In typing and shorthand subseries numerous articles were removed that were not written by Crawford. In the Professional Activities series, it was determined that all the folders that had to do with conferences, agendas and directories of various organizations could be removed as those materials could be found elsewhere and do not add to understanding Crawford and his contributions to I.U.
Business teachers --Indiana --Bloomington --History --Sources.; Business education --Indiana --Bloomington --History --Sources.; Indiana University. School of Business -- Faculty -- Archives; Crawford, T. James (Thomas James) -- Archives; Crawford, T. James (Thomas James) -- Correspondence
- Teaching, 1944-1986; Undated (Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Because the Teaching series contains student information, it is restricted. Folders requested by researchers will first be reviewed by an archivist as they may contain personal information regarding students.
  - Course files, 1944-1986; Undated (Box 1)
    - B 413 Business Education, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 503 Foundations of Business (Box 1)
      - Educational Policies Commission, 1944-1946 (Box 1)
      - Eastern Business Teachers Association 'Basic Principles of Business Education', April, 1949 (Box 1)
      - Bibliography, 1961 (Box 1)
      - 'Bibliography of Readings in Education', 1961 (Box 1)
      - Foundations, Miscellaneous Materials, 1962-1976 (Box 1)
      - Business Education Enrollments, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
      - Enrollment Status of Vocational Education in Indiana, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
      - Foundations of Business Education, II Semester, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
      - Foundation of Business Education, Reading List, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
      - The Counselor and Business Education, Business Education Forum, May, 1963 (Box 1)
      - Foundations of Business Education, General Reference List, 1963 (Box 1)
      - Ratio of Subject - Field Class- Period Enrollments to Total High School Class – Period Enrollments, 1963 (Box 1)
      - Foundations (Materials), 1964 (Box 1)
      - Selection and Guidance of Students for Technical and Vocational Education by Crawford, Margaret L., 1964 (Box 1)
      - Constitution and Bylaw of the Indiana Business Education Association, 1966 (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, 1969 (Box 1)
      - Associated Organizations for Teacher Education, Undated (Box 1)
      - Commission on Life-Adjustment Education for Youth, Undated (Box 1)
      - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Undated (Box 1)
      - 'An Experiment in Teaching Portable Electric Typewriting to Third and Fourth Grade Students' - Rowe, Undated (Box 1)
      - A Fierce Commitment, Undated (Box 1)
      - Foundations of Business Education "The Conant Report", Undated (Box 1)
      - Guidance for Business Education, Undated (Box 1)
      - Principles of Business Education, (National Business Teachers Association, Eighth Yearbook, 1942), Undated (Box 1)
      - National Business Education Association - Organizational Chart, Undated (Box 1)
      - Outlines and Bibliography, Undated (Box 1)
      - Position Paper #2: Distributive Education, Undated (Box 1)
      - 'The Price and Purpose of Education', Undated (Box 1)
      - 'The Purposes of Education in American Democracy', Undated (Box 1)
      - 'Recommendations Regarding the Implementation of the Provisions of Public Law 88-210 as They Relate to Vocational and Technical Education for Business and Office Occupations', Undated (Box 1)
      - Reading List, Undated (Box 1)
      - Some Criteria for Evaluating Cooperative Part Time Programs in Business Education, Undated (Box 1)
      - The White House Conference on Education, Undated (Box 1)
      - Writing Tips, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 504 Curricular Materials and Practices In Business Education (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, 1969 (Box 1)
      - Bibliography, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 523 Improvement of Instruction in Basic Business Education, Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 524 Typing Methods (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, 1969 (Box 1)
      - Fall, 1969 (Box 1)
      - Indianapolis, Spring, 1970 (Box 1)
      - Fall, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
      - Intensive II - Indianapolis, Improvement of Instruction in Typewriting, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Improvement of Instruction in Typewriting, Indianapolis; Intensive I, 1980 (Box 1)
      - Final Exam - Indianapolis, May 24, 1983 (Box 1)
      - Course Outlines, Undated (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1)
      - Reading List, Undated (Box 1)
      - Typewriting Methods, Test Questions RE: Instruction, Undated (Box 1)
      - Typing Methods - Miscellaneous Articles, monographs, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 526 Improvement of Instruction in Shorthand (Box 1)
      - Improvement of Instruction in Shorthand, Summer, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Shorthand Methods Lecture Materials, Undated; (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - B 527 School of Business Course Proposal - Improvement of Instruction in Data Processing, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 550 Master's Seminar in Business Education (Box 1)
      - Masters Seminal Indianapolis, 1985 (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 605 Administration and Supervision, Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 606 Current Problems in Business Education (Box 1)
      - Business Education, 1973 (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 650 Research Seminar In Business Education, Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 750 Doctor's Seminar in Business Education (Box 1)
      - Spring, 1970 (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
      - Doctors Seminar Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 753 Problems Seminar in Business Education, Course Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - B 790 Doctor's Research in Business Education, Course Outline, 1969 (Box 1)
    - C 204 Written Communication in Business (Box 1)
      - Comparison with W231 Course level, 1980 (Box 1)
      - Business, McCain, Undated (Box 1)
      - Written Communication in Business, Undated (Box 1)
    - C 220 Typewriting, Mid-Term Typing Examination, T9-22C, Undated (Box 1)
    - C 222 Beginning Typewriting II, 1967 (Box 1)
    - C 225 Intermediate Typewriting (Box 1)
      - Intermediate Typewriting, 1972 (Box 1)
      - Timed Writing Scale, 1972 (Box 1)
    - C 226 Intermediate Typewriting, 1975 (Box 1)
    - C 290 Office Organization and Management, Undated (Box 1)
    - C 300 Office Management II (Box 1)
      - Curriculum: Office Management, 1967 (Box 1)
      - Outline - Hershey, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - C 400 Management of Data Systems, Course Outline, 1978 (Box 1)
    - C 404 Office Systems and Control, David, 1971 (Box 1)
    - C 413 Methods of Employee Training (Box 1)
      - Indianapolis - Course Outline, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Syllabus, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Eli Lilly Training - Classroom Technique, Undated (Box 1)
      - Employee Training "Principles of Psychology...", Undated (Box 1)
      - "Methods" Used in Training, Undated (Box 1)
      - Principles of Psychology, Undated (Box 1)
      - Production in Office Work, Typewriting Training Program, Undated (Box 1)
      - Traits for Director Bloomington, Undated (Box 1)
    - C 502 Management of Support Systems, Course Outline, 1976 (Box 1)
    - C 504 Administrative Support Systems, Outline, Undated (Box 1)
    - C 506 Seminar in Office Management (Box 1)
      - Course Outline, 1969 (Box 1)
      - Day-by-Day Act. Hershey, Undated (Box 1)
      - David Programming, Undated (Box 1)
    - M 415 Class, 1954 (Box 1)
    - M 444 Methods of Teaching Business Subjects, Education, 1970 (Box 1)
    - M 460, Methods of Teaching Typewriting (Box 1)
      - Fall Semester, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
      - Exam 460971, 1971 (Box 1)
      - Typewriting Methods - Undergraduate, 1971 (Box 1)
      - Exam, Methods of Teaching Typewriting, 1973 (Box 1)
      - Exam, September 27, 1974 (Box 1)
      - Fall Examinations, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
      - Spring, 1975 (Box 1)
      - Fall, 1977 (Box 1)
      - Typewriting Methods - UG - Fall, 1979 (Box 1)
      - Undergraduate Exam, Lab in Teaching Type and Shorthand, October 14, 1981 (Box 1)
    - UG 54 Typewriting Methods - Undergraduate Exam, Undated (Box 1)
  - Shorthand, 1960-1984; Undated (Box 1)
    - An Analysis of the Frequency of Brief Forms and Principals and Abbreviating Devices In Gregg Shorthand Manual Simplified, Functional Method, Undated (Box 1)
    - The Area of Secretarial Training, Undated (Box 1)
    - Articulating Programs Preparing for Business Occupations, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Assignments - Shorthand, Undated (Box 1)
    - Basic Considerations in Adopting a Shorthand System, Undated (Box 1)
    - Basic Vocational Business Writing - J.E. Silverthorn Study, Undated (Box 1)
    - Building Speed by the Pyramid Plan, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Business Education in Indiana, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Calendar for the Gregg Shorthand Manual Simplified (60 day), 1960 (Box 1)
    - Century 21 - A New Primary Alphabet, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Century 21 Speedforms and Common Phrases, Undated (Box 2)
    - Comparisons Between Gregg - Gregg Papers, Undated (Box 2)
    - Copies of 1984 Exam - Shorthand (Box 2)
    - Credit by Exam Production Test - 7390 (K930), Undated (Box 2)
    - Dictation Chart Showing Length and Percent of Accuracy on New Materials, Undated (Box 2)
    - Dictation Drills, Assignment 62, Undated (Box 2)
    - Grubb's Stair Step Plan of Speed Building, Undated (Box 2)
    - Guidance Service for Pupils Electing Shorthand - Eyster, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Lesson 20 and 20-D, Century 21 Shorthand, Undated (Box 2)
    - Notehand Bloomington High School, Undated (Box 2)
    - Silverhorn Study - Syllable Intensity Analysis, 1964 (Box 2)
    - The Teaching Cycle in 1st Semester Shorthand, Undated (Box 2)
    - Transcription Program in Advanced Shorthand, Undated (Box 2)
    - Transcription Studies, Undated (Box 2)
  - Typewriting, 1949-1985; Undated (Box 2)
    - Developing Production Typewriting Ability, Undated (Box 2)
    - Discriminative Methodology, Undated (Box 2)
    - Drills for Building Basic Skill, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Dvorak Keyboard: Report and Articles, Undated (Box 2)
    - Experimental Plan, Undated (Box 2)
    - Increasing Office Typing Efficiency Through a Planned Program of Productive Typing, Undated (Box 2)
    - An Indirect Approach to Speed Building, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Issues in Teaching Typewriting, Undated (Box 2)
    - Japanese Typing Test, 1966 (Box 2)
    - T. Kimote - Correspondence about International Typewriting Contest Rules, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Letters Test, Undated (Box 2)
    - Materials for Typewriting Monograph, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
    - Maximize Vocational Typing Competence - TJC, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Measuring Problems Typing, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Measuring Production Typing Skills - Beaumont, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Problem Skill Building Materials, TJC, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Production Test Handouts, Undated (Box 2)
    - Psychological Concepts Germane to Efficient Motor Skill Development in Typing – Linsday, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Psychological Phenomena Related to Typewriting, Undated (Box 2)
    - Related Learning Materials, Undated (Box 2)
    - Research Paper in Typewriting, Undated (Box 2)
    - Results in Typewriting, Undated (Box 2)
    - Skill Deterioration Study - Returns, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Special Drill Materials, Undated (Box 2)
    - Special Speed Building Materials - TJC, Undated (Box 2)
    - Special Speed Building Paragraphs - TJC, Undated (Box 2)
    - Standards of Achievement, Undated (Box 2)
    - Teaching Production Typewriting, Undated (Box 2)
    - Technique Improvement Drills, Undated (Box 2)
    - Typewriting, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Typewriting Learning and Instruction, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Typewriting Motion Drills, Undated (Box 2)
    - Typing Rates, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Typewriting Survey, Undated (Box 2)
    - Undergraduate Typewriting Methods, November, 1961 (Box 2)
  - General, 1947-1986, Undated (Box 2)
    - An Annotated Bibliography of Selected Reference Relating to Cooperative Part-Time Methods, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Bibliography, Undated (Box 2)
    - Center for Research and Development in Education for High-Level Technical Positions, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Continuing Education - Proposal for School to IHEC, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Dr. H. D. David, 1970-1986 (Box 2)
      (RESTRICTED)
    - Education - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2)
    - Graduate Courses - Suggestions for Preparation of Written Assignments, Undated (Box 2)
    - Guest Lecture - Mr. Charles Chasteen, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Kuiper, Shirley (Dr.), Undated (Box 2)
    - Materials for Duplication, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Questions Submitted by Teachers, Undated (Box 2)
    - Schedule and Enrollment, 1947-1963; (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Student Teaching, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
    - Teaching Materials - Miscellaneous, Undated; (2 folders) (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1947-1987; Undated (Box 2)
  - Australia - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Chandra Lynn (Baker), 1977 (Box 2)
  - Arffa, Elaine (Mrs.), 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - University of Strathclyde, Miss Mary Bannatyne, September, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Batchelder, H.T., 1956-1964 (Box 2)
  - Bell, Robert P., Undated (Box 2)
  - Bray, Esther, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Bray, Esther (Correspondence), 1979 (Box 2)
  - Bray, William G., I. U. Foundation, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Brinson, Al, 1976 (Box 2)
  - C - Correspondence, 1955-1977 (Box 2)
  - Crawford, 1958 (Box 3)
  - D - Correspondence, 1951-1969 (Box 3)
  - David, Don, 1967-1982 (Box 3)
  - David, H.D., 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Departmental Administration (Box 3)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Departmental Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Departmental Communications (Box 3)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 3)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 3)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Departmental Faculty Individual Memos, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Departmental Memos (Box 3)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 3)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Dillon, Jacqueline, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Dvorak, Earl, 1967-1977 (Box 3)
  - E - Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 3)
  - Ellis, Richard, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Enloe, James (Education Department), 1977 (Box 3)
  - Everard, Dr. Kenneth, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Eyster, Dr., 1968-1971 (Box 3)
  - Eyster Scholarship Fund, 1966-1978 (Box 3)
  - F - Correspondence, 1958-1969 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3)
  - G - Correspondence, 1947-1969 (Box 3)
  - General, 1947-1987; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Gibbons, Helen, 1967-1972 (Box 3)
  - Gousha, Dean Richard P., 1975-1979 (Box 3)
  - Gregg Publishing Company, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Grill, George P., 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Gros Louis, Kenneth, Vice-President, Indiana University (Bloomington), 1980 (Box 3)
  - Grossack and Martin Project (Box 3)
    - General, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Textbook Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 3)
  - Hershey, Gerald, 1968-1973 (Box 3)
  - Hulburt, Jack - Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Interdepartmental Communication, 1959-1980 (Box 3)
  - Kissick, Merrill D., 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Letters - Responses Required, 1983-1987 (Box 3)
  - Library, 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - Lomax, Paul, 1952-1956 (Box 3)
  - M - Correspondence, 1955-1969 (Box 3)
  - Mathis, John, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Martin, Ken, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - McReynolds, Shirley, 1977-1981 (Box 3)
  - Moseley Letter, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Moses H. Cone Memorial Hospital, 1953-1955 (Box 3)
  - N - Correspondence, 1954-1967 (Box 3)
  - National Association for Business Teacher Education (NABTE), 1947-1976 (Box 3)
  - National Office Management Association (NOMA), 1960-1966 (Box 3)
  - O - Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 3)
  - O'Neil, Robert M., Vice President, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - P - Q - Correspondence, 1952-1970 (Box 3)
  - Person, Marjorie, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1958-1963 (Box 3)
  - Pinnell, Dean, School of Business, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Poole, Alice (Personnel), 1982 (Box 3)
  - R - Correspondence, 1948-1968 (Box 3)
  - Reigner, Charles G., 1957-1960 (Box 3)
  - Request for Information, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
  - Rutherford, Janet, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Ryan, John, (Indiana University President) (Box 3)
    - Complaint Letters, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 3)
  - S - Correspondence, 1952-1970 (Box 3)
  - School of Business Faculty Members - Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 3)
  - School of Education - Memos, Notes, 1963-1981 (Box 3)
  - Scifers, Jo Ann, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Scott, Foresman and Company, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Social Studies Proposal, 1963 (Box 4)
  - T - Correspondence, 1955-1969 (Box 4)
  - U - V - Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box 4)
  - United States Achievement Academy, 1987 (Box 4)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - W - Correspondence, 1953-1968 (Box 4)
  - Waltz, Loren, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Wentworth, Dean, 1984 (Box 4)
  - White, Kathy, 1978-1985 (Box 4)
  - Wyllie, Eugene, 1967-1977 (Box 4)
  - X - Y - Z - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
- Professional activities, 1948-1986; Undated (Box 4)
  - Professional organizations and conferences, 1948-1985; Undated (Box 4)
    - Administrative Management Society (Box 4)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 4)
      - 1973-1975, (2 folders) (Box 4)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1980 (Box 4)
    - American Society for Training and Development, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - D.D. Lessenberry, Speaking Engagements Information, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Delta Pi Epsilon (Box 4)
      - General Materials, 1948 (Box 4)
      - Nominees for Membership, 1968 (Box 4)
      - Research Foundation - Meeting, November 8 and 9, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Fresno State - Summer, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Indiana Business Education Association (Box 4)
      - 1960, (2 folders) (Box 4)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 4)
      - 1980 (Box 4)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 4)
    - Indiana Business Educator's Club (Box 4)
      - 1970-1982 (Box 4)
      - 1979 (Box 4)
    - Indiana State Committee on Business Education, 1970 (Box 4)